When you can't breathe, you can't scream.
Anaconda is a adventure, horror, thriller film directed by Luis Llosa.
A 'National Geographic' film crew is taken hostage by an insane hunter, who takes them
along on his quest to capture the world's largest — and deadliest — snake.
Terri Flores, played by Jennifer Lopez.
Danny Rich, played by Ice Cube.
Paul Serone, played by Jon Voight.
Dr. Steven Cale, played by Eric Stoltz.
Warren Westridge, played by Jonathan Hyde.
Gary Dixon, played by Owen Wilson.
Anaconda is a 1997 action adventure horror film directed by
Luis Llosa and written by Chris Broodryk.
The film stars Jennifer Lopez, Ice Cube, Jon Voight, Eric
Stoltz, Jonathan Hyde, and Owen Wilson.
An international co-production between the United States and Brazil, the film focuses on a documentary film crew in the
Amazon rainforest that is led by a snake hunter who is hunting down a giant, legendary green anaconda.
The film received generally mixed reviews, but was a box office
success, and has become a 1990s cult classic.
It is the first installment in the Anaconda film series.
The film explores themes of human vs nature, snake,
predator, movie business, expedition.
The tone is dark and intense.